{
  "type": "identification",
  "instructions": "Identify what is being asked in the following sentences.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "Question": "Description of what services that system is expected to provide and the constraints under which it must operate.",
      "Answer": "User requirements",
      "Alt-Answer": null,
      "Points": 3
    },
    {
      "Question": "Detailed information about the system functions, services and operational constraints that are to be implemented.",
      "Answer": "System requirements",
      "Alt-Answer": null,
      "Points": 3
    },
    {
      "Question": "Statements of the services that a system should provide, how the system should react to particular input and how the system should behave in particular situations.",
      "Answer": "Functional requirements",
      "Alt-Answer": null,
      "Points": 3
    },
    {
      "Question": "Constraints (timing, performance, reliability, development process, standards) on the services or functions offered by the system; normally apply to the system as a whole.",
      "Answer": "Non-Functional requirements",
      "Alt-Answer": null,
      "Points": 3
    },
    {
      "Question": "Creation of a simple working model of system to show users what requirements may look like when implemented.",
      "Answer": "Throwaway prototyping",
      "Alt-Answer": null,
      "Points": 3
    },
    {
      "Question": "Its main goal is to build a very robust prototype in a structured manner and constantly refine it.",
      "Answer": "Evolutionary prototyping",
      "Alt-Answer": null,
      "Points": 3
    },
    {
      "Question": "Way of structuring requirements to represent perspectives of different stakeholders.",
      "Answer": "Viewpoints",
      "Alt-Answer": null,
      "Points": 3
    },
    {
      "Question": "Graphical representations that describe the business process and the system to be developed.",
      "Answer": "Analysis Models",
      "Alt-Answer": null,
      "Points": 3
    },
    {
      "Question": "Official statement of system requirements.",
      "Answer": "Software Requirements Specification",
      "Alt-Answer": "SOA",
      "Points": 3
    },
    {
      "Question": "Defines a generic structure for a requirements document.",
      "Answer": "IEEE",
      "Alt-Answer": "The Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers",
      "Points": 3
    },
    {
      "Question": "Assessment of the quality of the requirements.",
      "Answer": "Requirements Validation",
      "Alt-Answer": null,
      "Points": 3
    },
    {
      "Question": "Process of identifying, understanding, tracking and controlling changes to system requirements.",
      "Answer": "Requirements Management",
      "Alt-Answer": null,
      "Points": 3
    },
    {
      "Question": "Stakeholders who influence the requirements.",
      "Answer": "Indirect viewpoint",
      "Alt-Answer": null,
      "Points": 3
    },
    {
      "Question": "People or systems that interact directly with the system.",
      "Answer": "Interactor viewpoint",
      "Alt-Answer": null,
      "Points": 3
    },
    {
      "Question": "Domain characteristics and constraints that influence the requirements.",
      "Answer": "Domain viewpoint",
      "Alt-Answer": null,
      "Points": 3
    }
  ]
}